Fausto Rosado

New York, NY • 718-536-9149 • fausto.rosado@icloud.com • www.linkedin.com/in/fausto-codes

Summary

Professional with 15 years of work experience in the federal government, customer service, sales, research, teaching, homeless outreach, technical/software development.

Languages: HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, Ruby, Python.

Webtools: PostgreSQL, SASS, AJAX, Restful API, Active Record, Ruby on Rails.

EXPERIENCE

HelloTech, multiple locations Computer/IT Technician

Apr 2019 - Oct 2020

• Performed over 600 jobs for individuals and companies ranging from IT/technical support, smart home installation, computer networking, advanced computing; mobile; advanced networking including enterprise; smart firewall; POS setup & smart home security.

BronxWorks Homeless Outreach Team, Bronx, NY **Senior Case Manager**

May 2013 - Mar 2019

- Through direct outreach in a social service relationship, identified over 200 chronically homeless individuals.
- Direct psychiatric referrals and treatment for persons with untreated mental illness; liaison with Human Resources Administration; 35 individuals placed into permanent housing.

Bureau of the Census, New York, NY

Fall 2013 - Oct 2019

Field Representative/Enumerator (Intermittent)

• Gathered economic data for the Census across three quantitative surveys and questionnaires in English/Spanish for individuals and businesses in New York and New Jersey.

Federal Emergency Management Agency, Brooklyn, NY Community Relations Specialist

Oct 2012 – Sept 2013

• Disaster recovery case management for families affected by Hurricane Sandy across Brooklyn.

South Bronx Classical Charter School, Bronx, NY

Sept 2010 – June 2012

Learning Specialist

Helped develop best practices for student special-needs instruction in Grades 3-5.

Cision US Inc., New York, NY

Spring 2001 – Oct 2010

Public Relations Specialist / Editor

- Media Research: database management system (DBMS) for PR clients.
- Sales (5+ years) of public relations solutions through Cision Point proprietary platform.
- Led a team that transcribed and monitored broadcast media and social networks.

EDUCATION

• The Knowledge House, Bronx, NY, Data Science Apprenticeship 2020 - 2021

New York Code + Design Academy, Manhattan, NY, Software Engineering
 Nov 2018 – Feb 2019

• **CUNY – Lehman College,** Bronx, NY, Psychology 1998-2003